

CAREER VISION

Seeking a challenging, responsible and dynamic position in renowned organization where all my energies, knowledge and experience can be effectively utilized for benefit of the organization and enhancement of my career.

CONTACTS

Q Lahore, Pakistan

+92 324 7770106

f-dev@outlook.com

S gejawad

Leadership

https://onfusion.github.io/

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication

Team Work

Creativity

Dedication

Confidence

Jawad Bhatti

Sr. Consultant Salesforce / Front-End / UI Developer

PROFILE

Creative Front-End Developer offering 9+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Over the past 9 years, as a Front-end Developer, I have designed, developed, and launched customized, highly responsive websites and e-commerce solutions using advanced technologies. In addition, I have consistently met client expectations and project milestones while working effectively in deadline-driven environments.

TECHNOLOGY & FRAMEWORK

- SFCC, SFRA, Demandware
- Material UI, Semantic UI
- React JS

- Twitter Bootstrap
- Angular JS, Angular
- Vue JS, Knockout JS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML/HTML5
- SASS/LESS, Compass
- Pug JS
- TypeScript
- Gulp, Grunt, Webpack
- WordPress, Shopify
- UI/UX Designing

- CSS/CSS3
- jQuery
- JavaScript
- Git, SVN, GitHub
- Node JS, NPM, Yarn
- PHP, MySQL
- Photoshop

WORK HISTORY

Systems Ltd.

Lahore 2021 - Present

Sr. Consultant Salesforce

Provide Salesforce Commerce Cloud (SFCC) technology expertise for solution design and technical implementation. Design, code, unit test, and code review iterative improvements to platform.

Zepto Systems PVT Ltd.

Islamabad 2015 - 2021

Sr. Front-End Developer

Worked closely with programmers and clients to meet project requirements, goals, and desired functionality. Developed and integrated customized themes into WordPress, Drupal, and PHP based web applications.

Sitara InfoTech PVT Ltd.

Faisalabad 2014 - 2015

Web Developer

Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages and CMS including WordPress. Developed websites from front to backend using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, and PHP.

EDUCATION

2021

Master's Degree

Virtual University of Pakistan

2009 - 2011

Bachelor

Punjab University of Lahore

2007 - 2009

Intermediate

P.B.T.E of Lahore, Pakistan

2006 - 2007

Matric

B.I.S.E Faisalabad, Pakistan

CERTIFICATION

2015

Web Development

EVS Learning Faisalabad, Pakistan.

2013

Web Designing

ApTech, Pakistan

2011

CCA (Course of computer application)

TEVETA - P.B.T.E Lahore, Pakistan

LANGUAGE

English

Urdu

Digital Solution PVT Ltd. Jr. Web Developer

Faisalabad 2013 - 2014

Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates by 40%. Performed there for outsource projects based on WordPress CMS.

IT Empire PVT Ltd.

Faisalabad 2011 - 2013

Jr. Web Developer

Performed in this organization as Jr. developer, operate several websites based on B2Evolution, WordPress and Joomla CMS.

PROJECTS

KaDeWe

Salesforce (SFCC/SFRA), Node JS https://kadewe.de/

QS Hub

Angular JS, Node JS, PHP https://qs-hub.qs.com/

Top Universities

Drupal, JavaScript, SCSS, PHP https://www.topuniversities.com/

KTech Solutions Ltd.

WordPress, JavaScript, PHP http://www.ktechsol.com/

Movein 4

PHP Zend Framework, Knockout JS https://poilet.mymovein.com/

QS - Quacquarelli Symonds

WordPress, JavaScript, PHP https://www.qs.com/

Top MBA

Drupal, JavaScript, SCSS, PHP https://www.topmba.com/

HOBBIES / INTEREST



Computing



Photography

0



Travel



Music